hello friends welcome to the Realty
Express and Express to your wealth
creation those to Hodges video my parrot
cage over this penny stock super couch
detail analysis getting a skill-shot
seduced to East occupy up Kiki our
strategy one inch a year a skipper may
up Naik point-of-view up Lucas Archer
carnival ah who totally doses should
look at the hair subset belly to those
to me a blue cookie some neat
calculation Rockne Allah who is
Kamehameha follow Goethe a piece which I
had to follow cursor to YESCO completely
ignored because active dojo swapnika
yapper portfolio hair actor of market
leader said those two or actor of penny
stocks a may uplift fun cookie I say
allocate karoonga
a mirror Franken 99% to find those to
market leaders skip a stagger or SIF
eight percent goes to a penny stock
yacuiba stocks Cooper up allocate curse
active eastern us example get all pedals
to upkeep a second o'clock a portfolio
hair was messy a ninety-nine thousand
rupees to add those to market leaders
see a quality stocks Cooper Janet a year
or bark Iike a Hazara pay a penny stocks
yeah kisi will be stocks you put up
allocate curse active oh it's case arts
at the get up cut this has Alka
portfolio those two nine thousand nine
hundred rupees upkeep market leaders
yeah quality stocks cupid's energy or
sorbet those to a penny stock equity
stocks you put up allocate constructive
yeah egg formula he chose to do me
hamesha follow kurta who have escucha
hito follow curse active YESCO
completely ignored because a to ask a
Godot so Micucci important parameters P
ro ke saamne Rockne Allah who is the
belly up logos a request karoonga get up
is channel pin Yahoo to please his
channel go subscribe ecology or
notification well I can commit the body
G da Chiesa video ski update upcoming
that hey so you have it also accompany
coach parametric's go check it later
here market kept those two 3860 car or a
cup tomatoes to a year's talk jabber
this really pay here fifty five point
forty three percent can return three
month pay those two thirty point seventy
one percent can return one year made
also 7.16 can return teens are Meadows
to you negative return there I eleven
point seventy eight percent can return
five years may 198.50 four percent can
return or ten years Meadows to three
hundred and twenty four point thirty
three percent return so you happy though
stop short term media Jes talked about
this really pay here is case are charged
up yes yes talk those two to long-term
age a te
yes talk those two negative returned
then I start
Dean sales methods to a negative return
their eyes or pastured the Salma does to
a positive return there but return as
compared to the short-term those two
body come make you happy to the next
parameters could gel this is the clay
they is talking about to last time the
quantity trade was a 4 K rool 61 legs
11,000 321 shares key quantity trade who
were the its major delivery of high gear
those two to corrode 46 slacks
eighty-six thousand five hundred and
forty-six years key delivery of high
gear or delivery key percentage of those
two fifty three point fifty four percent
yet delivery report those two Kalka here
yabba-doo so next parameter Scobie am
jalisa check a letter company capacitors
to shear holding pattern cup check
earlier promoted skippers also seventy
one point six percent keys over this
holding a december key quarter maybe
yeah he holding tau or march cake water
maybe same holding hair up gently see
those two FIA ski holding could be
deadly their fi skippers goes to two
point sixteen percent key holding a
December quarter may March kick water
and ethic goes to two point zero five
percent key holding ho gayi any FIA stay
point eleven percent key holding come
cardia hey the is key building Kobe
deglet ATI skippers point zero seven
percent key holding December K
Quartermaine or mark a quarter on ethic
dos 2.0 four percent key holding any dia
Steffi point zero three percent key
holding co-come Kerdi I have mutual
friend Kiku I be holding near those so
is stock Cooper or others narrows to the
ecology
twenty six point sixty nine percent key
Jabbar this holding lyric here is
tortoises talk to you / December cake
water may job mark a quarter Anitha
close to twenty six point eighty three
percent key holding ok yah yah yah yah
pH is happening notice Kyoko those two
FIA CIA's make up a stock u / exit
career F is di small pitch key market
cynical rare or Jew normal Omni Vishakha
those two his stock or Java accumulate
career to is parameters co-op the harm
in Iquitos to FASD is capacity artists
tools rate a in key research team OTA
agora acid the good institutions agree
stock to / exit career or amnesia close
to is taco or accumulate career - yeah
bodyguard but those two mutual friend
key BKB investment in a stock paper
though yeh egg parameters could be up
the handmade exceptive up jaleesa those
two company key results comedic let that
late in quarter car September gear
quarter made those two 1341 December
quarter my 1000
- or March kick waters that goes - 991
key sales performance the Calle up
operating profit by those two September
cake water my 258 December cake watered
my 140 or March kick water may 146 up
hapax is happening notice Kyogre
operating profit with those two december
key quarter key comparison may do last
quarter to the March mania cha
performance care KD kya net profit could
be objectively J September gig or
quarter may 140 or December quarter me
37 or mass 2020 k coordinate those so
forty any applaud your performance to
head to those two last quarter
comparison me his company nature
performance decay decay I am though yeh
important parameters say to me hablo
poca Sam LaRocca Nakata of jalisa dosto
company K balance sheet per could be a
bad check ility company K reserves those
to the except it's the last three years
ago March 2018 me 2,228 March 2019 the
sole company name or reserve parody
update 2,475 or March 20 2009 that goes
to 2523 can reserve courtesy hi company
name Yanni here on year company up the
reserves Coburn RA is Kasasa death
Scooby check early their March 2018 is
also company cat dead Jota
2,798 Abby March 2020 quarter and ethic
dosto company neck jaw versus
up net debt coca mccurdy Ayane 1629 kid
dead ho gayi to a being bought the
important parameters those 2 German a
blue cookie Sam Lee Ratna Ratna Chaotica
a be happy dosto company Konami logo
potato Trident limited ake a penny stock
it also is company to break news at the
Trident on Tuesday received a patent for
woven fabric with improved comfort by
the United States Patent Office patent
office to its new skipper those two eggs
about this really hey stocky upper fill
all those to make up Lucas say requests
karoonga
AB new school soon k stock Cooper
objects a up need a guitar be or
delivery report me sorry low-key stock a
peachy Bihari those two op Kamisha grant
me recognize a year to Warren Buffet
surname patata be fearful when others
are greedy be greedy when others are
fearful to up kupatana t those - sorry -
look the bog restore capital aqua a
beast occupant jelly body in he cannot a
year I feel I'll wait and watch
strategic Assad is talk of noir
this may add kiddie to yet a mere
opinion is Tokyo per Bakke may up locus
request Kirk Wiebe investment decision
Lena say Pele a please kisi financial
advisors say consult curry with Kabaddi
qui decision Li acceptable to Toledo's -
thank you very much for watching this
video
a gorilla video pass and aya please
subscribe to my channel and hit the bell
I can also to melt ahead levy do pay J
Hin